wegetworld.com 2012-11-12

# Privacy & security - Shopping Cart Software & Ecommerce Software Solutions by CS-Cart

**Privacy & Security**

**WeGetWorld.com's Privacy Policy**

**WeGetWorld.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We hope that you will take the time to read this policy, which explains what information we collect from you and how we use that information. By using our website or by purchasing products or services from us, you agree to be bound by this policy. Please check back frequently, as this policy may change from time to time.**

**What information we collect and how we use it** When you visit our website, WeGetWorld.com collects your IP address, which we use to improve our products and services as well as to help us administer our website and diagnose technical problems.   
Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information that does not personally identify you.   
To receive our website's newsletters and/or periodic email notifications with special offers, you only need to leave your email address with us. However, to order from us, you must set up a WeGetWorld.com account by providing us with your name, email address and a chosen password.  
 These constitute your "Account Information".   
Account Information also includes any information that you may provide to us in response to customer surveys. When you place an order with us, we will also collect your shipping address and telephone number, as well as credit card number, billing address, and card expiration date, if applicable. This information constitutes your "Order Information". Order Information is necessary for us both to process your order and notify you of your order status.   
Order Information also includes any information that you provide us in connection with an order that you later cancel or that is not completed for any reason. We may use your Account Information and Order Information to occasionally notify you about important changes to the website, new WeGetWorld.com features, special WeGetWorld.com offers that you may find useful, or offers from companies with whom we have business relationships. We may also contact you if you have entered one of our contests or sweepstakes, or responded to one of our surveys. Choosing not to receive email newsletters or email notifications from us when you enter a contest or sweepstakes will not affect your chances of winning. If you would prefer not to receive email newsletters or email notifications from us (other than email notifications relating to order processing), simply visit the "Preferences" section of "My Account". From here, select "Newsletter Subscriptions" and/or "Personalized Email Reminders and Special Offer Email Subscriptions," indicate which newsletters or email notifications you wish to unsubscribe from, and then click the "Update" button. ****

**How we protect your information** To protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control we have implemented security measures at this website. When you place orders or access your account information, a secure server is employed. All information you input is encrypted by the secure server layer (SSL) before it is sent to us and all the customer data we collect is similarly protected against unauthorized access. WeGetWorld.com will not share your personal information with third parties unless you have consented to the disclosure or the disclosure is necessary to: (1) Comply with the law or with legal process, or with requests from law enforcement authorities;(2) Protect and defend our rights and property;(3) Protect our customers or users from misuse or unauthorized use of the WeGetWorld.com website; or (4) Protect the personal safety or property of our customers or the public. ****

WeGetWorld.com may share your personal information with other companies in our corporate group. Also, if WeGetWorld.com is acquired by or merges with another company, WeGetWorld.com may transfer personal information to that company. In such an event, WeGetWorld.com will notify you before your personal data is transferred if this information would become subject to a materially different privacy policy.

WeGetWorld.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related website information to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information. Put simply, while we will not tell our business partners that a particular individual bought a particular product, we may, for example, tell them how many customers within certain demographic groups bought certain products.

A website traffic and user behavior auditing system operated by Google Analytics is being used on this website. Please see Google Analytics websitef or information about Google Analytics, the Google Analytics auditing system, and Google Analytics' privacy policy.

**Making changes to your information** You may change your personal information on file with WeGetWorld.com at any time. To do this, simply visit the "Account Management" section of "My Account". From here, choose "Change your Sign In and personal information", "Manage Shipping Addresses in your address book", and/or "View and change your Credit Card Profiles". Enter the changes to the information as desired, and then click the "Update", "Edit", or "Delete", button, as appropriate. ****

**Links to other websites** The WeGetWorld.com website contains links to other sites, operated by third parties that we believe may be of interest to you. While WeGetWorld.com encourages third parties to follow appropriate privacy standards and policies, it is not responsible for the actions of those parties, the content of their websites or any products or services they may offer. ****

**Cookies** The WeGetWorld.com website employs "cookies," which are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies enable us both to provide a Shopping Cart and to store your shipping and billing information between visits. ****

If you have set your browser to reject cookies, you can still use our site, although you may need to re-enter information that would normally be obtained from the cookie.

Our affiliates or advertisers may also use cookies and though WeGeWorld.com encourages anyone who uses cookies to follow appropriate privacy standards and policies, it is not responsible for cookies placed by third parties.

**Children's privacy online** At WeGetWorld.com, we believe that the privacy of children is important. We do not monitor the age of our user audience except in connection with surveys and contests, and except for age data optionally provided by users who wish to customize their account preferences, However, visitors and users under the age of thirteen (13) should not submit personal identifying information to WeGetWorld.com without the consent of their parent(s) or guardian(s). ****

If you are a parent and want to limit your children's access to material you believe may be harmful to them, you may want to look into commercially available hardware, software and filtering devices. Relevant information can be found at http://www.safetysurf.com/ and other similar sites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** Please check back frequently, as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. The date of the most recent update to the Privacy Policy will be indicated at the top of this page. In the event of a material change to the Privacy Policy, we will add "Updated", "New", or a similar term near the link to the Privacy Policy on the home page of WeGetWorld.com and elsewhere throughout the site. ****

**Questions/SuggestionsIf** you have any questions or suggestions, please contact us at services@hmein.com or by mail at the address below: ****

Ho Sung Cho / CEO & President  
HM e-International Co., Ltd.  
2nd Floor, Doowon Bld, 218-11 Jangan-Dong  
Dongdaemun-Gu, Seoul, South Korea  
Tel. +82-2-6351-0049  
Fax. +82-70-7862-0588
